♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x14 ♪
The Empathy Optimization
Original Air Date on February 4,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)That's not her.
That's not her.
Really?
(Leonard:)The old Asian man
is not your Meemaw?
(Sheldon:)And that's not helpful.
You know, I-I got her
an iPhone for Christmas.
(Sheldon:)I'll see where she is.
(Leonard:)Oh, that's nice.
(Leonard:)Most people her age
don't embrace technology.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, she doesn't
even know she has it.
(Sheldon:)No, I had my sister
slip it in her bag
(Sheldon:)so that I can track her
like a sea turtle.
(Leonard:)Same as when we lost you
at the zoo.
(Sheldon:)Uh, for the hundredth time,
(Sheldon:)I smelled kettle corn
and couldn't find the cart.
(Leonard:)Still doesn't explain
(Leonard:)how you ended up
on the freeway divider.
Moon Pie!
Meemaw!
I'm so happy to see you!
I'm happy to
see you, too!
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)You got even smaller.
I love it!
(Sheldon:)Uh, Meemaw, this is Leonard.